(Penny:)Yeah, you did.
(Penny:)I felt so self-conscious,
I had to return them.
(Bernadette:)Where? To Babies R Us?
You're doing it again!
(Bernadette:)Okay, sorry.
Can we just go?
(Bernadette:)I feel like
everybody hates me.
(Penny:)Oh, come on,
they don't hate you, all right?
(Penny:)They're just
a little intimidated.
(Penny:)All you need to do
is show everyone
(Penny:)how sweet you really are.
(Bernadette:)I think I'd
rather go.
No, come on.
(Penny:)You are not going anywhere,
all right?
(Penny:)I am here for you, and we are
gonna fix this together.
(LeVar Burton:)Thank you.
(Penny:)Even though your dress is ugly.
(Sheldon:)Well, my little Flag-keteers,
(Sheldon:)it looks like the last episode
of Fun with Flags is at an end.
(Sheldon:)If I could,
(Sheldon:)I would run each and every one
of you viewers up a flagpole
(Sheldon:)and salute you.
(Sheldon:)And if you touched the ground,
burn you.
(Sheldon:)I'd like to take a moment
(Sheldon:)to personally thank
Dr. Amy Farrah Fowler,
(Sheldon:)who you may
or may not know
(Sheldon:)is the first woman to co-host
a flag or banner-related